http://www.bighorngolf.com/privacy-policy/

HomePropertiesClubhousePenthouseThe VaultAmenitiesGolfSpa & WellnessFive-Star CuisineEventsTransportationFamily FirstConciergeThe Jewel BoxMembership5 Minutes to EverywhereBIGHORN MagazineThe BIGHORN LegacyPhilanthropyContact UsCareers
HomePropertiesClubhousePenthouseThe VaultAmenitiesGolfSpa & WellnessFive-Star CuisineEventsTransportationFamily FirstConciergeThe Jewel BoxMembership5 Minutes to EverywhereBIGHORN MagazineThe BIGHORN LegacyPhilanthropyContact UsCareers
BIGHORN Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs your use of the website, and explains, in general, what Personal Information and other information is collected from and about you, how the information is used, and with whom we may share such information. By visiting this website, and/or using the services offered on or through this Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as they may be amended from time to time. The services on this website may change and expand, and this Privacy Policy may change accordingly, so check back occasionally. This Privacy Policy is part of, the BIGHORN website terms and conditions which governs your use of this website in general, and the BIGHORN affiliate terms and conditions, which governs your use of and participation in the BIGHORN affiliate program.
This Privacy Policy does not apply to information that you may provide, or that we may obtain, other than through our Website, such as by phone, through postal mail and through other live and print media. This website is intended for users who are located in the United States of America. This privacy policy shall be interpreted under the laws of the United States.
Advertisements and other content that may be displayed or transmitted to you on or through the website may be customized to your interests and preferences, based on your personal information and website usage information, including (but not limited to) non-personally identifying information, which we may obtain from you or from other sources.
Privacy Policy Purpose
Your privacy is important to BIGHORN. To make your visits to our website and use of the services available as purposeful as possible, you may be asked for personal information and certain information may be collected from your computer when you visit us. â€œPersonal informationâ€ includes, for example, your name; home and/or business address; e-mail address; telephone number; credit card and other payment information; social security number or employer identification number; demographic information and/or other information that may identify you as an individual or allow online or offline contact with you as an individual.
Right to Opt In and Opt Out
You may have the right to opt in and opt out of certain of our uses of your personal information. For example, at the time you are requested to provide personal information on this website, you may have the opportunity to elect to, or not to receive correspondence from us. You may opt out of any communication with BIGHORN by clicking the opt-out link in our communications, or by sending an email to info@BIGHORNGOLF.com stating that you would like to be removed from a specific BIGHORN list, or all communications. Please understand that you may be contacted by BIGHORN in connection with your relationship with us as a client, or as follow up from an event, class, or purchase.
BIGHORN Collects the Following Information
User-Provided Information
We collect Personal Information from and about users of our website, for example, through such users™ activities, transactions and completion of online forms on our website. Such information is collected, for example, when users register or subscribe for accounts or features on our website (including, for example and without limitation, membership in The Elite Entrepreneur Club or registration in our affiliate program), make online purchases, complete surveys, post to or comment on our blog that we may make available on or through our website, submit a comment or question to us using a â€œcontact usâ€ or similar feature on our website, send us an e-mail, or in any other way submit personal information to us via our website. You may be able to send information about our website, products and services to your peers, contacts, friends, and family members through our website by clicking on a â€œTell A Friendâ€ or similar button on our website or in an e-mail we have sent to you. In some cases (unless you simply forward our e-mail on your own), you may provide the name and e-mail address of your contact to us. That information will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable law.
Website Use Information
Cookies. We may use â€œcookiesâ€ to keep, and sometimes track, information about you. Cookies are small data files that are sent to your browser or related software from a web server and stored on your computerâ€™s hard drive. Cookies track where you travel on our website and what you look at and purchase. They may store your preferences, the information in your shopping cart, and/or your username and/or password. A cookie may enable us to relate your use of our website to other information about you, including your personal information. All of these purposes serve to improve and personalize your experience on our website. Most web browsers can be set to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, the Website or certain areas or features of the Website.
Clear GIFs. We may use clear GIFs (pixel tags) or similar technologies, in the website and/or in our communications with you to enable us to know whether you have visited a web page or received a message. A clear GIF is typically a one-pixel, transparent image (although it can be a visible image as well), located on a web page or in an e-mail or other type of message, which is retrieved from a remote site on the Internet enabling the verification of an individualâ€™s viewing or receipt of a web page or message. A clear GIF may enable us to relate your viewing or receipt of a web page or message to other information about you, including your personal information.
IP Address and Click-through Information
Our server collects data about your serverâ€™s Internet address automatically when you visit us. This information, known as an Internet Protocol address, or IP Address, is a number thatâ€™s automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever youâ€™re on the Internet. When you request pages from our website, our servers may log your IP Address and sometimes your domain name. Our server may also record the referring page that linked you to us; the pages you visit on this website; the website you visit after this website; the ads you see and/or click on; other information about the type of web browser, computer, platform, related software and settings you are using; any search terms you have entered on this website or a referral site; and other web usage activity and data logged by our web servers. We use this information for internal system administration, to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Such information may also be used to gather broad demographic information, such as country of origin and Internet Service Provider. We may also link this information with your personal information. Any or all of these activities with regard to website usage information may be performed on our behalf by our services providers.
How BIGHORN Uses Your Personal Information:
BIGHORN will use your personal information, for example, to respond to your requests and to provide you with our product and service offerings. We may also use your Personal Information to maintain our internal record keeping. We may match information collected from you through different means or at different times, including both personal information and website usage information, and use such information along with information obtained from other sources, including third parties. In addition, we may send you notices (for example, in the form of e-mails, mailings, and the like, such as our e-newsletters), and otherwise correspond with you, about products, services, companies and events, sponsored by us and others, that we think might interest you. You may opt out of receiving such notices from us by following the instructions in the right to opt in and opt out section above. We may analyze user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our Website and e-mails, both on an individual basis and in the aggregate. In general, other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy, we do not share Personal Information with third parties.
Service Providers
We may use third-party partners to help operate our website and deliver our products and services, and may share your information with our affiliates, service providers and other third parties that provide products or services for or through this website or for our business (such as website or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, e-mail service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies, and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf).
Aggregate Statistics
We may disclose aggregate statistics regarding user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our website and e-mails to third parties in the form of aggregate data, such as overall patterns or demographic reports that do not describe or identify any individual user.
Legally Compelled Disclosures
We may disclose user information to government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities, at our discretion, or otherwise as required or permitted by law, including but not limited to in response to court orders and subpoenas. We also may disclose user information when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users of the website, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.
Business Transfer
In the event that BIGHORN, or substantially all of its assets, is acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, consolidation or liquidation, user information may be one of the transferred assets.
Security
While BIGHORN will endeavor to protect the security and integrity of sensitive personal information provided to this website, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers. If you contact us by e-mail or a â€œcontact usâ€ or similar feature on our website, you should be aware that your transmission might not be secure. A third party could view information you send by these methods in transit. Do not send sensitive information (such as payment card information, social security numbers, employer identification numbers, passwords, or pin numbers) to us via e-mail or via a â€œcontact usâ€ or similar feature on our website. We will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties during or after transmission. In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your personal information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail. You consent to our use of e-mail as a means of such notification.
Consent to Processing
By providing personal information to this website, you understand and consent to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other countries and territories.
Third-Party Linked-To Websites
When you are on our website you may have the opportunity to visit, or link to, other websites, blogs, or other electronic media not operated by BIGHORN. These sites may collect personal information about you. BIGHORN does not control sites that are operated by these entities and is not responsible for the information practices of the other websites. The privacy policies of any linked websites are the sole responsibility of the other websites.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
BIGHORN reserves the right to change or update this privacy policy, or any other of our policies or practices, at any time, and will notify users of this website by posting such changed or updated privacy policy on this page. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to this website. Under certain circumstances, we may also elect to notify you of changes or updates to our privacy policy by additional means, such as posting a notice on the front page of our website to sending you an e-mail.
Contact BIGHORN
If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy practices, you may contact us at:
BIGHORN
535 Mesquite Hills, Palm Desert, CA 92260
